litemind.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Litemind

This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at Litemind.com. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you accept the practices described here.

## Collection of Information

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example, to add you to one of our mailing lists.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Litemind does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include…

  * Google Adsense
  * Commission Junction
  * Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Litemind send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Litemind has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Litemind’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Distribution of Information

We do not share your personally identifiable information to any third party for marketing purposes. However, we may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.

## Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized staff of this site (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

## Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact Litemind by using the [contact page](https://litemind.com/contact/ "Contact Litemind").

 _Policy last updated on **3-Apr-2009**. Litemind reserves the right to make changes to this policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. _
